{
  "chapter": 20,
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "Amazon Web Services is which type of cloud computing distribution model?",
      "incorrect_answers": ["IaaS", "PaaS", "SaaS", "All of these"],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Azure is which type of cloud computing distribution model?",
      "incorrect_answers": ["IaaS", "PaaS", "SaaS", "All of these"],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Google’s cloud service offering for launching virtual machine is",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Elastic Compute Cloud",
        "Azure VM",
        "Compute Engine",
        "App Engine"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Microsoft’s cloud service offering for Big Data solution is",
      "incorrect_answers": ["DynamoDB", "DocumentDB", "BigQuery", "SimpleDB"],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "The service offered by Azure cloud for Big Data analysis is,",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "HDInsight",
        "Elastic MapReduce",
        "BigQuery",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "OneDrive storage facility offered by Microsoft Azure is a",
      "incorrect_answers": ["IaaS", "PaaS", "SaaS", "None of these"],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Which hypervisor is used by AWS for its data center resource visualization?",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Hyper-V", "KVM", "VMware’s ESX", "Xen"],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the storage services of Google is comparable with Azure OneDrive?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Google Cloud Storage",
        "Google Drive",
        "Google Cloud Data store",
        "All of these"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Google Cloud Storage and Google Drive are respectively",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "IaaS and IaaS",
        "IaaS and PaaS",
        "SaaS and IaaS",
        "IaaS and SaaS"
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Which among the storages of AWS is the home for general purpose EC2 instances?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Solid-state device",
        "Simple Storage System",
        "Elastic Block Storage",
        "All of these"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Azure Hypervisor is a customized version of which among the following?",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Hyper-V", "Xen", "VMware’s ESX", "KVM"],
      "answer": 1
    }
  ]
}
